<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>paglaadmins &#8211; US Get Greenshot</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.getgreenshot.org/author/paglaadmins/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.getgreenshot.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 20:32:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Venice sees Polanski, Bradley Cooper but only on-screen</title>
		<link>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/venice-sees-polanski-bradley-cooper-but-only-on-screen/</link>
					<comments>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/venice-sees-polanski-bradley-cooper-but-only-on-screen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 20:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.getgreenshot.org/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Roman Polanski and Bradley Cooper headline the Venice Film Festival on Saturday, though controversy and a Hollywood strike mean neither is attending. Still technically a fugitive from US justice over a child sex conviction in the 1970s, the 90-year-old Polanski will be absent for the premiere of ‘The Palace’, his farce set in a Swiss ... <a title="Venice sees Polanski, Bradley Cooper but only on-screen" class="read-more" href="http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/venice-sees-polanski-bradley-cooper-but-only-on-screen/" aria-label="More on Venice sees Polanski, Bradley Cooper but only on-screen">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roman Polanski and Bradley Cooper headline the Venice Film Festival on Saturday, though controversy and a Hollywood strike mean neither is attending.</p>
<p>Still technically a fugitive from US justice over a child sex conviction in the 1970s, the 90-year-old Polanski will be absent for the premiere of ‘The Palace’, his farce set in a Swiss hotel that could be the legendary director&#8217;s last film.</p>
<p>An ongoing actors strike in Hollywood means Cooper and Carey Mulligan will also be missing from the launch of their movie ‘Maestro’ about legendary conductor and composer Leonard Bernstein and his wife.</p>
<p>Though Cooper is also director, he chose to stay home in solidarity with the strikers, foregoing the splashy red carpet launch he gave his previous hit, ‘A Star is Born’, in Venice.</p>
<p>There has been some internet-driven controversy over Cooper&#8217;s decision to wear a large prosthetic nose &#8212; seen by some as perpetuating stereotypes about Jews &#8212; though Bernstein&#8217;s family defended the film and said the composer would not have minded and confirmed he had a &#8220;nice, big nose&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8216;Full of criminals&#8217;<br />
Since the MeToo movement, Polanski&#8217;s conviction for child sex in the 1970s has overshadowed his work and made him a pariah in Hollywood.</p>
<p>Still revered for classics like ‘Chinatown’, ‘Rosemary&#8217;s Baby’ and ‘The Pianist’, his selection in the out-of-competition section at Venice has been widely criticised by feminist groups and others.</p>
<p>His new film stars Mickey Rourke and John Cleese as guests in a fancy hotel for the turn of the millennium.</p>
<p>For decades, Polanski&#8217;s conviction was largely overlooked, particularly in Europe where he continued to work and win awards, right up to his last film, the France-based ‘An Officer and a Spy’, which won the Jury prize in Venice in 2019.</p>
<p>But anger over that film&#8217;s success at France&#8217;s Cesar Awards proved a rallying point for MeToo anger in the country, which had been a haven for the director for years, especially as fresh assault allegations against Polanski came to light.</p>
<p>Venice festival director Alberto Barbera defended the decision to include him, telling AFP: &#8220;The history of art is full of artists who were criminals, and we nonetheless continue to admire their work.&#8221;</p>
<p>‘Maestro’ is among 23 films competing for the Golden Lion in Venice, to be decided on 9 September.</p>
<p>A towering figure of 20th-century classical music, Bernstein assured his place in popular history by composing the Broadway smash musical ‘West Side Story’. The Venice competition has one frontrunner so far after rave reviews for ‘Poor Things’ on Friday.</p>
<p>It saw Emma Stone as a sexually voracious reanimated corpse in a darkly comic, and strongly feminist, reimagining of Frankenstein. In response to the low-fat trend of the 1990s, numerous food businesses removed saturated fats from their products, only to replace them with sugars to retain palatability.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, the new products were no healthier than the originals, and the average individual now consumes far too much saturated fat.</p>
<p>Also getting warm reviews was Adam Driver as racing car impresario Enzo Ferrari in Michael Mann&#8217;s ‘Ferrari’.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/venice-sees-polanski-bradley-cooper-but-only-on-screen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hardik, Ishan help India come out of trouble against Pakistan</title>
		<link>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/hardik-ishan-help-india-come-out-of-trouble-against-pakistan/</link>
					<comments>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/hardik-ishan-help-india-come-out-of-trouble-against-pakistan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 20:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.getgreenshot.org/?p=9</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ishan Kishan on Saturday became the second India wicketkeeper-batter to score four successive scores of fifty or more as he made a doughty 82 to bring India out of trouble during Asia Cup 2023 clash against arch-rivals Pakistan at Kandy. The left-handed batter walked in at number five, with Men in Blue in trouble at ... <a title="Hardik, Ishan help India come out of trouble against Pakistan" class="read-more" href="http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/hardik-ishan-help-india-come-out-of-trouble-against-pakistan/" aria-label="More on Hardik, Ishan help India come out of trouble against Pakistan">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ishan Kishan on Saturday became the second India wicketkeeper-batter to score four successive scores of fifty or more as he made a doughty 82 to bring India out of trouble during Asia Cup 2023 clash against arch-rivals Pakistan at Kandy.</p>
<p>The left-handed batter walked in at number five, with Men in Blue in trouble at 66/4 in 14.1 overs.</p>
<p>Ishan joined forces with all-rounder Hardik Pandya to help Team India recover from a difficult situation.</p>
<p>Ishan-Pandya partnership helped India cross the 200-run mark. However, the left-handed batter started to struggle due to cramps. This made him to go for big shots as running between the wickets became difficult. The 138-run stand between the two was broken as Ishan’s mistimed shot landed in the hands of skipper Babar Azam. Kishan was dismissed for 82 (81 balls), which included nine fours and two sixes off the bowling of Haris Rauf.</p>
<p>This was Kishan’s seventh half-century in ODIs. This is also his fourth successive score of 50 or more in ODIs.</p>
<p>Earlier, during the series against West Indies in July-August, Ishan had notched scores of 52, 55 and 77 in three ODIs. His 184 in three matches at an average of over 61 gave him the &#8216;Player of the Series&#8217; award.</p>
<p>Before him in 2011, MS Dhoni had scored four half-centuries in a row from September-October 2011. He had scored 69, 78*, 50*, 87* against England.</p>
<p>Sachin Tendulkar, Virat Kohli, Suresh Raina, Navjot Singh Sidhu and Sourav Ganguly are other players who have scored four successive fifty-plus scores for India.</p>
<p>Tendulkar, Rohit Sharma and Virat Kohli have also gone a step further as they are among the names having scored five successive fifty-plus scores for India. Among all these, Virat&#8217;s run of 133* against Sri Lanka, 108 against Sri Lanka, 66 vs Bangladesh, 183 against Pakistan and 106 against Sri Lanka in five straight ODIs is the strongest by an Indian in ODIs.</p>
<p>Pakistan&#8217;s Javed Miandad has record of scoring nine successive fifty-plus scores between March-October 1987, scoring 78, 78*, 74*, 60, 52, 113, 71*, 68 and 103, in a brilliant run of form.</p>
<p>India suffered some early blows as they lost the wickets of skipper Rohit Sharma (11), Virat Kohli (4) to Shaheen Afridi and Shreyas Iyer (14) and Shubman Gill (10) to Haris Rauf.</p>
<p>India won the toss in their opening game of the Asia Cup 2023 and opted to bat in the match being played at Pallekele Stadium in Kandy in Sri Lanka.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/hardik-ishan-help-india-come-out-of-trouble-against-pakistan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South African police kill 18 in shootout</title>
		<link>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/south-african-police-kill-18-in-shootout/</link>
					<comments>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/south-african-police-kill-18-in-shootout/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 20:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.getgreenshot.org/?p=6</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Police killed eighteen people in a shootout in South Africa&#8217;s northeast on Friday, saying they had targeted suspects who were planning to rob a cash truck. &#8220;As soon as police approached the address, the group of suspects began shooting, police retaliated,&#8221; the South African Police Service (SAPS) said in a statement. &#8220;Sixteen males and two ... <a title="South African police kill 18 in shootout" class="read-more" href="http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/south-african-police-kill-18-in-shootout/" aria-label="More on South African police kill 18 in shootout">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Police killed eighteen people in a shootout in South Africa&#8217;s northeast on Friday, saying they had targeted suspects who were planning to rob a cash truck.</p>
<p>&#8220;As soon as police approached the address, the group of suspects began shooting, police retaliated,&#8221; the South African Police Service (SAPS) said in a statement.</p>
<p>&#8220;Sixteen males and two females were declared dead at the scene.&#8221;<br />
A police officer was &#8220;injured very seriously&#8221; and taken for medical care, SAPS National Commissioner General Fannie Masemola told reporters in Makhado, Limpopo province, around 400 kilometres (250 miles) northeast of Johannesburg.</p>
<p>The shootout lasted for about 90 minutes, said Masemola.</p>
<p>According to police, who had been tracking the movements of the suspects for a few days, a probe began in January with the aid of the country&#8217;s intelligence unit.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our intention was to arrest them before they go out and commit the crime&#8221; Masemola said.</p>
<p>Cash truck heists happen regularly in the crime-ridden southern African country.<br />
Last year 10 suspects died during a cash-in-transit shootout with police after the would-be robbers fired at a police helicopter and wounded one of the pilots.</p>
<p>In May police minister Bheki Cele said there was a &#8220;stubborn increase&#8221; in cash-in-transit robberies of more than 20 percent, with 64 cases reported during the first three months of the year.</p>
<p>The crime statistics, which are presented by the minister every quarter in a live broadcast, have been steadily rising over the past few months in a country that has one of the highest crime rates in the world.</p>
<p>Police have said they are &#8220;clamping down on serious and violent crimes throughout the country&#8221;.</p>
<p>Four people who were found in &#8220;another safe house&#8221; were arrested in connection to the alleged cash truck robbery plan.</p>
<p>Masemola said there was also an &#8220;explosive that was ready to be used because they wanted to hit one of the cash depots in the province&#8221;.</p>
<p>He said the suspects planned to use an ambulance to transport the money to the country&#8217;s Gauteng province.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.getgreenshot.org/2023/09/02/south-african-police-kill-18-in-shootout/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
